(Spice Rice Cake)
(Space Rice Cake is closed today.)
(Well, because I don't have to cook today...)
(I almost finished all the food.)
(They enjoy a relaxing tea time.)
(The rice cakes come out great today.)
(But the joy of having a day off didn't last long.)
(Where did all the cameras go?)
(It makes me anxious.)
(Why don't I see any cameras?)
(Something feels off outside.)
(For some reason, their affection for Goheung deepens today.)
(Something feels wrong, but they choose to enjoy their day off.)
Are we going to the photo studio first?
What... Are we going to the photo studio first?
Yes, we're stopping by the photo studio, but first...
While you were making the rice cakes,
we got a call from the HQ.
What did they say?
- What's with that serious face?
- What did they say?
- We need to leave.
- The HQ...
I mean, you've been telling us some of the work issues.
The POS system.
(I really want the POS system!)
(Please.)
- Really?
- You wanted the POS system.
- What else?
- I want a part-timer.
- You wanted a part-timer.
- I really want that.
(Can you get a part-timer for us?)
(Post an ad on a secondhand market or something.)
(Hire a part-timer!)
(Come on!)
- The tables make it hard to serve.
- The tables.
And you also asked...
- for a waiting area.
- Yes.
- We told them about your requests.
- I see.
And the HQ says that, since you've been working so hard,
they want to grant your requests.
That's what they said.
Where has Young Ji been wanting to go since day one?
Seoul.
- Oh, I see... What?
- Seoul.
You said you wanted to go to Seoul.
- Why do you keep doing this to me?
- No way.
I mean, why... I just want to go up above the sky.
Why are you doing this to our king?
- Why do you keep doing this to me?
- But just earlier...
Only yesterday, you said you could...
- run a restaurant in Seoul.
- Are we going to Seoul?
(Are we going to Seoul?)
(Can we go to Seoul?)
This is how I feel, Mimi.
(We're now good enough to run a restaurant in Seoul.)
(Do you want to go to Seoul?)
(Yes.)
(She did go on about how she wanted to go to Seoul every day.)
So the HQ opened up the second branch in Seoul.
- What are you talking about? Now?
- This is ridiculous.
- Why would you do that?
- Are we going to Seoul?
Don't lie to us. Are we really going to Seoul?
It's true. The second branch is...
- Are we really going to Seoul?
- Come on. Don't lie to us.
- It's only been four days...
- No wonder.
- since we came here.
It's only been four days, but it's true.
Since you guys wanted to go to a busy neighborhood,
we picked a popular neighborhood, Yeonhui-dong.
It's located in the middle of Yeonhui-dong.
- Really?
- That's so close to my house.
The second branch...
(The youngest member is simply happy about going to Seoul.)
- That's so close to my house.
- She's thinking of going home.
But we provide shared housing for all of you...
- Oh, right. I know.
- as an employee benefit.
I want to stay with them in the same place.
- But that's not the problem.
- Right. Let's stay together.
- Why must we leave here?
- Exactly. I...
I just got used to this place.
- We have everything in the kitchen.
- Exactly. We just got used to...
- working in that kitchen.
- We got used to working there.
- I'm not doing this!
- Hold on.
- Let's go on strike.
- Hey.
- Why?
- We're going on strike!
- But why...
- But Young Ji, you said...
- You asked us to send you there.
That has nothing to do with this.
You said you wanted to go to Seoul.
- That's why they arranged this.
- I mean...
- If I had suggested the US...
- We just got used to working here.
Would we be going to the US if that was the case?
- Yes, we were going to do that.
- You see...
- We would've arranged that.
- Of course.
- I mean...
- They might change the plan again.
We might have to deal with another challenge.
- Do you want to go to the US?
- That brat...
Young Ji, do you want to go to the US?
Didn't you just say you wanted to go to the US?
- Your Highness, my dear princess...
- How about we...
travel across the US?
Please keep your mouth shut, Your Highness.
I love the idea of going to Seoul.
We should leave right now so we can start working there.
- Right now?
- We're going to Seoul today?
- My gosh. Hang on a second.
- We're going to Seoul now.
(She grabs the back of her neck in disbelief.)
(It's heartbreaking and funny at the same time.)
- Hold on.
- Are you okay?
I haven't even said goodbye to the stove yet.
You can do that now.
I have a question for you guys.
Why is it a challenge for the kitchen team...
to work in Seoul, not Goheung?
Listen to me.
We just got used to...
- how things work here.
- Okay.
- And I got attached to this place.
- I can't leave here.
- My point exactly.
I've only just settled into my work here.
Since you stabilized the business in such a short time,
the HQ wants you to do the same for the second branch.
They want you to work your magic there too.
You need to expand your business if you want to succeed, you know.
How the service team is okay with this makes me even more upset.
They're fine with this decision.
You can even use the POS system there.
That's really great. We're just so happy.
And we'll probably have standing tables there.
- Then give us just one minute.
- Go and say goodbye.
Say goodbye to the stove.
(Rushing)
Mimi.
(It feels empty in the kitchen.)
Guys.
- Take care.
- Guys.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye, guys.
One last time...
Let's have a look at them for the last time.
(They're saying goodbye to each and every ingredient.)
Guys.
Goodbye, deep-fryer.
I can't believe this.
I can't leave.
I've grown so attached to this place.
Why would everything I say come true?
What did I do so wrong?
You know that's not what I meant by "going to Seoul."
Why would they lie on the ground?
(Meanwhile, Yu Jin brings something with her.)
I really like the idea.
I'm going to take some photos.
(The service team takes photos to capture the memories.)
Let's go to the beach.
- To the beach?
- Yes.
This is legendary.
- Was it in the frame? Okay.
- Step back further.
(This part-timer is used to posing for photos.)
- Was it okay?
- Look at the photo I just took.
(She's so good at taking photos.)
This vibe... This is what I'm talking about.
(This time, Yu Jin takes photos of Eun Ji.)
(Chuckling)
You look stylish, Eun Ji.
(While the service team is busy posing and taking photos...)
How can I leave all these behind and go to Seoul?
There's good equipment in Seoul too.
So I should just abandon my beloved equipment here?
How am I supposed to abandon my precious equipment...
(Groaning)
(Clutching the back of her neck to control her rising blood pressure)
Hold that pose and look down.
Make it look like you're tucking your hair behind your ear.
Your Majesty,
- I beg you to understand them.
- How dare you...
treat your king this way?
Do we have more tables there?
- Probably.
- You'll see when you get there.
Find out when you get there.
Let's rip this off and pack it with us.
- Like this.
- Yes.
- Just lift it up.
- Like this.
We have even better ones there.
It has to be this one.
Exactly. I can't use any other stove.
Wait. They're taking photos.
They'll take some photos for about ten minutes...
and go to pack their stuff.
(Closing her eyes for photos)
Let's hurry up and have some photos taken.
Goodbye, my friend.
(To the kitchen equipment)
My beloved friend.
For some reason, the rice cake...
It's still warm.
What do we do?
(And then she cries her heart out again.)
What's wrong with the kitchen team?
(She feels ticked off by them for no reason.)
What are you doing right now?
(What are you doing right now?)
Say goodbye and come on out.
We have to run the second branch...
(Screaming)
Hurry up and pack your... Hurry up and come out already.
Come on out.
(She walks toward her beloved kitchen tools again.)
You worked here only for four days. Why are you...
We have those in Seoul too.
Young Ji and Mimi!
- The cleaver?
- Yes.
Why would you pack the cleaver?
We have a cleaver in Seoul too.
All right. Let's get going.
Let's go home now.
- Are we really leaving like this?
- Yes.
We can have the photoshoot in Seoul if you want.
- We can hang out here a little...
- Okay.
and just stop by the general store. What do you want to do?
- Won't you do the photoshoot?
- I'll do that.
Mother.
- Let's get going.
- Let's go.
(She reluctantly steps out through the gate.)
(She grabs the open sign on her way out.)
One, two, three.
(They bring the sidewalk sign inside.)
We're heading to the second branch.
- Goodbye.
- We're going to the second branch.
Goodbye, Goheung.
- Let's go to the second branch.
- Okay.
You need to pack your bag quickly so you can enjoy shopping...
and do the photoshoot. Let's go.
We can "enjoy shopping."
What's the point of shopping at the general store?
All their stuff has the Goheung vibe.
Guys, let's just stop by the photo studio.
We won't even get to visit the general store.
Are we just leaving like this?
The stuff at the general store has the Goheung vibe. Right, Yu Jin?
- Absolutely.
- They have the Goheung vibe.
Are you going to buy some chairs and take them to Seoul?
We don't need to stop by there.
How do we carry all those to the airport?
- All right.
- Good. Let's not visit the store.
- Then we...
- We'll only visit the photo studio.
Father, why are you so powerless over them?
I wanted to have a look around the store.
Since we're going to sleep together,
I'll tell you about the store at night.
- We're going to sleep together.
- Will you describe it vividly?
- So I can picture it in my mind?
- I'll make sure of it.
I'll be by your side one night, and by Mimi's side the next.
And the next day...
- We'll leave at 3pm, guys.
- Got it.
Hurry up and come in.
(Everyone is rushing inside to pack their bags.)
Come on in already. We don't have time for that.
(She sighs deeply and plops down on the floor.)
I feel so hollow.
Mimi, take off your gloves and mask.
- Eun Ji.
- You feel so hollow?
(She feels bad for Mimi.)
Are you tearing up?
(She's practically wailing.)
What's the matter?
It's good that we get to introduce our food to people in Seoul, right?
- That's true.
- Right.
I know you're right. You're absolutely right.
- You know that, but still feel sad.
- That's right.
Gosh. I don't want to leave.
Why are you so sad, Young Ji?
Are you that upset?
Seriously, why am I so upset? I really don't want to leave.
(She's sad to go, right when she settled into the work here.)
I'm so used to working in that kitchen.
- You have a lot of love in you.
- Right.
I just got used to working here.
I'm sure they'll set up the new kitchen...
the exact same way as the one here.
(The 2 kitchen team members managed to pack up and step outside.)
At least we're not going overseas. That's a relief, right?
Maybe that would be better.
- Don't say such a thing.
- Got it.
- Maybe that would be better?
- All right.
Why only my words...
Why do only my words turn into reality?
(Why do only my words turn into reality?)
- Hello.
(Getting on the bus)
(The 2 kitchen team members drag their heavy feet.)
- Hello.
- Get on the bus.
She's one cold-hearted woman.
Hello.
Why are you looking so sad?
Good job, you guys. It's always hard to say goodbye to what you love.
Saying goodbye is never easy, but let's try to do it with a smile.
I'm okay.
- This parting will break our hearts - Break our hearts
(But it will be graceful)
(Saying goodbye to Goheung breaks our hearts.)
(But we say goodbye to welcome another challenge!)
(I wouldn't mind regretting making rice cakes.)
(So we're saying goodbye to Goheung.)
(Goodbye to the rainy day when it poured)
(Goodbye to the customers who came all the way here)
(Goodbye to those little moments we shared)
(The Goheung branch was meaningful as it was our first restaurant.)
(Goodbye)
(Closed for business)
Are we going to stop by the photo studio?
Yes, we'll stop by the photo studio and then head to the airport.
I want to go straight to the airport.
- Won't you do the photoshoot?
- I will.
(I should do what I have to do.)
You will, right?
This is how little kids behave when they're sulky.
- "So you really won't do it?"
- "I will."
(Mimi, the kid, is sulky after losing her restaurant.)
We're leaving.
What's the final tally for our sales?
- Is it 1,200 dollars?
- It's over 1,000 dollars.
Is it about 1,300 dollars?
What are we going to do with that money?
- Let's put it into SK Hynix.
- Let's do that.
Let's invest the money in stocks.
They say ETFs are better.
- Right.
- Let's say we have 1,300 dollars.
How much is that if we split it four ways?
It's...
But SK Hynix might reach 160,000 dollars a share in a year.
I mean, we don't have much of seed money.
We're going to make more money this week...
- We'll put it all into SK Hynix?
- Yes.
Let's buy the stocks when we make 3,000 or 4,000 dollars.
- Will you execute the trades?
- Yes.
I do want to get a new phone.
(Chuckling)
- You bought that one recently.
- It's all cracked.
(Use of Funds 2: Buying a new phone for Yu Jin)
- It's too heavy.
- You can put a phone case on it.
It'll be too heavy.
Is going caseless a trend...
among young people these days?
You're not on the younger side.
- I'm old-fashioned.
- You're on the older side.
- I'm on the older side.
- I'm young and trendy.
- Is this considered trendy?
- I'm old-fashioned...
- This is old-fashioned too.
- No, that's...
Mimi got her feelings hurt so many times today.
(The backstabbing staff and ruthlessly blunt younger members)
You don't have to say she's old-fashioned.
Mimi...
(Punishing)
- It's so funny that Mimi said...
- The temperature is...
she wanted to open the restaurant today.
When will you take your mask off, Young Ji?
I'm going to keep it on a bit longer.
She needs someone else to do it for her. Eun Ji can do it.
I thought you would keep it on too.
- Eun Ji helped me take it off.
- Yes, I did.
- Give me some belly rubs.
- Why?
So I can feel at ease.
(She's so worried about working in Seoul that she might develop IBS.)
Mimi...
Mimi just asked for belly rubs so she could feel at ease.
(Rubbing her belly)
(Falling)
Gosh, you shouldn't have brought those utensils.
- Did it fall down?
- It fell down, Young Ji.
- Why would you...
- You weren't even holding it.
How are you going to board the plane with all that stuff?
They're going to set off the metal detector repeatedly.
(How could you say that right in front of my utensils?)
- Seriously.
- What's wrong with you?
You can easily find those at any dollar store.
Why did you bring them with you?
I couldn't just abandon my hometown friends.
Should I abandon them because there are smarter ones in Seoul?
Just take them with you.
We were going to buy a hose at that store.
- And a large basin.
- Exactly.
Is that the general store?
- No, it's a hardware store.
- No, it's...
- It's a hardware store.
- They sell toilets?
- There's a sauna over there.
- It's on your right side.
- Y Sauna.
- Right, there's Y Sauna too.
There are so many stores here. Isn't it like a whole new world?
- Yes, it is.
- It's amazing.
- We're here.
- Let's get off the bus now.
Grab what you need for the photos when you get off the bus, okay?
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Hello.
- Hello. It's nice to meet you all.
We're here to take a family photo, just like this one.
- Which one?
- This one right here.
Oh, would you like the family photo theme?
- Like this. With this background.
- Yes. I like this background.
Young Ji, how about you wear this?
I want to wear it.
How about Young Ji wears this?
(Young Ji immediately puts it on, giving off middle-aged man vibes.)
(Yu Jin is glamming up too.)
(Mimi brought her own prop.)
It's good, right?
(The photoshoot begins.)
Don't try to look pretty. Try to look sentimental.
(A sentimental smile?)
Can you move the ladle a bit to the side?
Move the ladle...
One, two.
One more time. One, two.
(Closed for business)
I'll take it.
(Only the Goheung branch is closed.)
- Your expression looks better now.
- One, two.
(We still have the Seoul branch to run.)
(Checking the photos)
What's with that face?
Why did you show your teeth like that?
(She expressed her sadness by showing her teeth.)
We're holding hands.
I like this photo.
I like... It's a great photo.
I really like this one.
The three of you have such glowing skin.
Did you not apply lotion this morning?
- Who?
- You, Young Ji.
- I'm wearing makeup too.
- It's just...
Your skin looks natural and smooth.
- It's cute. The size is different.
- One of each.
Let's make sure we never lose this photo.
- Let's keep it safe.
- Okay.
(What kind of memories will they make in Seoul?)
(Yeosu Airport)
(The Earth Arcaders arrived at Yeosu Airport.)
(They boarded the flight carrying the utensils and the open sign.)
(Departure: Yeosu Airport)
(Arrival: Gimpo International Airport)
(They set off for the Seoul branch!)
Gosh, this is insane.
I was just selling tteokbokki in Goheung, but now I'm here...
This must be a dream. Isn't it?
- It's a dream, right?
- It's a dream.
- This is ridiculous, seriously.
- I just took a nap, right?
But what am I wearing? What are these?
(They were in Goheung just 2 hours ago.)
- This is...
- We're closed for business.
A lot of new things have been set up at the second branch.
- I'm so excited.
- We'll give you a little tour...
- and explain everything to you.
- Okay.
Is there anything you're expecting to see there?
- What we're expecting to see there?
- Yes.
- A robot that can do a flip.
- Sorry?
(Young Ji is dreaming of a state-of-the-art restaurant.)
I wanted a robot...
Is there anything else you want to see there?
- No.
- Nothing else?
I'll be happy if we just have the POS system.
- Just the POS system?
- It'll solve all the problems.
We won't be embarrassed...
in front of the customers anymore.
The POS system sounds great.
Do we have a couple more serving carts?
- Serving carts?
- Yes.
The one you used in Goheung was too loud.
(The street lit up brightly while they were sharing their wishes.)
- Guys, this neighborhood is...
- We're actually in Seoul.
- There's O Store.
- This is a totally different world.
You're right. Look at that, guys.
We were in the countryside.
Hey, we're in the city now. What should we do?
- It sure is so bright.
- It's bright, indeed.
Night has already fallen, but it's still so bright.
You're right. Girls, what do we do about this?
(Seoul)
(With a population of over 9 million)
(A place packed with countless people)
(Just as bustling as it is crowded)
(Filled with different vibrant landmarks...)
(and dazzling culture)
(In this complex city of Seoul)
(The neighborhood where Earth Arcaders run their business)
(Yeonhui-dong)
(Between low-rise buildings and old alleyways)
(You'll find trendy restaurants everywhere.)
(The neighborhood is constantly bustling...)
(with food lovers.)
(What kind of food experience will Space Rice Cake introduce?)
There's Shinchon Central Baptist Church.
(The Mapo-gu resident is starting to get excited.)
If you go up this way,
there's a nice charcoal dry sauna in Sinchon.
- There's a charcoal sauna?
- Yes.
This place looks familiar. Wait a minute.
It's that gimbap restaurant.
- We're in Yeonhui-dong.
- Yes, we are.
There's even Yeonhui-dong Barbershop.
My favorite bakery is in Yeonhui-dong.
- Which one?
- Which bakery?
- What kind of bread?
- They have cream bread.
Cream bread?
- We're here.
- Let's go.
Please get out of the car.
Young Ji, I'm so nervous.
Me too.
Hold on. Why is it in such an open space?
(Intimidated)
Oh, no.
- My legs are giving out.
- What do we do?
Is this where our second branch is?
- My legs are giving out.
- There will be so many people.
(They get out with a mixture of suspicion and anticipation.)
What's this?
- What's going on?
- What's this?
Wait, this is a pop-up store.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
(Space Rice Cake)
(Welcome. Isn't this your 1st time at the 2nd branch?)
- This is impossible.
- Isn't this a pop-up store?
Eun Ji, there are two stories.
- What do we do?
- Wait.
(You can tell at a glance how much bigger it is.)
- Wait, this is too big.
- Girls, what do we do?
- How many tables are there?
- Get rid of that.
Anyone can tell that it's us.
It's so obvious.
- What do we do?
- My goodness.
- I didn't see it being constructed.
- It's way too big.
Young Ji, wait for me.
- Let's pretend not to know.
- Wait.
- Hold on.
- This is the way to paradise.
- To paradise.
- We're going to paradise.
- "Stairway to Heaven."
- It looks pretty.
- There will be a waiting line here.
- What do we do?
(In awe)
The first floor isn't part of the restaurant.
(When you open the red gate, you'll find...)
(A counter)
This place probably has an online reservation system too.
- My gosh.
- We do have the system.
- We do?
- I'm so glad.
- That's amazing.
- Is this the POS system?
(The POS system they had been dreaming about)
(Even a state-of-the-art reservation system has been installed.)
- This is incredible.
- I'm so glad.
This is incredible.
Is this the POS system?
This place is really nice.
Here's the kitchen.
(Past the counter...)
That's incredible.
(The kitchen team's biggest interest)
The equipment looks great.
Wait, how many burners are there?
- What is this?
- One, two, four... Six burners.
- Wait, Young Ji.
- There are nine burners.
There are nine burners?
- Nine burners?
- Should I be happy or worried?
- What is this?
- Mimi.
- This is so convenient.
- Seriously.
- They installed something new.
- This is really nice.
What? It's really nice.
This is for sukiyaki, right?
- It's really nice.
- We must be selling hamburgers.
- This kitchen is no joke.
- I love the fryers.
- There are two of them.
- Yes.
Look how much bigger the dishwashing sink is.
- What's this?
- The dishwashing area.
Oh, my gosh.
(Just in case, there's an additional dishwashing area.)
- I prefer this.
- Is this the place?
(The floor manager immediately checks the water pressure.)
- I prefer this.
- Really?
There are chairs here.
I like it.
These are all Torong's clothes.
Oh, my.
(The waiting area requested by the service team)
- My gosh.
- These must be our uniforms.
They look pretty.
- They're cute.
- The uniforms look so cute.
(And staff uniforms for the 2nd branch)
- They're cute.
- The uniforms are pretty.
They're cute.
- They're really cute.
- This is amazing.
- There's a photo area.
- It's so cute.
- This is really cute.
- I love it.
You point the camera up like this.
(Look up at the sky and capture a memory before you leave)
This looks amazing.
This place is really nice.
Do we have to climb the stairs?
I don't think there's an elevator at the restaurant.
(The 2nd floor dining area for the customers)
Yu Jin, this is really great.
- There's a self-service station.
- Self-service?
- Self-service.
I'm so grateful.
- I'm very grateful.
- I'm grateful for the self-service.
(The basic tableware set up in one corner)
I'm truly grateful.
(Further inside on the 2nd floor)
(The main hall)
(The secondary hall)
There are so many.
- What do we do?
- There are so many tables.
One, two,
three, four, five.
Seven, eight, nine.
Where are the others?
There are nine tables.
(There are more tables to match the bigger scale.)
(They're starting to feel a little down.)
(There are meaningful drawings of different dishes.)
We must be selling hamburgers.
Are we selling pizzas too?
Then we won't be able to start business right away.
(Will their prediction come true?)
We have a lot to learn today.
How are we supposed...
- to carry the food over here?
- To climb up the stairs...
I know. The stairs are so steep.
Eun Ji, can you carry the food?
We'll have to carry it carefully while engaging our buttocks.
Eun Ji.
What do we do? There are nine halls.
- What do we do?
- There's another sink here.
The vibe here has changed quite a bit.
Here's what we will do tomorrow.
You're all influential people, so I'm sure...
you've been to something like this.
A brand launch event.
- Have you been there?
- Like a pop-up store?
- You can find it at pop-up stores.
- I haven't been to any.
It's where they set up a photo wall.
That's happening here tomorrow.
Our second branch launch event.
You mean, for us?
- A photo wall?
- A photo wall.
We had an opening event in Goheung, remember?
We'll set up something like that here.
It'll be at 1pm. Dress to match the vibe here.
You can go to the salon beforehand if you want,
or you can get your outfit fitted.
- It's up to you.
- I want to look pretty.
This place is amazing and beautiful.
- For now...
- Congratulations.
Thank you, everyone.
- You must've worked very hard.
- For such an amazing place...
Right. Thank you for giving us an incredible space.
The scale is no joke.
(They head to their accommodation.)
I know.
There are too many wicked spirits around here.
Every time I'm in front of the burners, I hear them.
Everyone does.
Speaking of wicked spirits, I have a question.
Don't you hear them in the dining area?
Don't you hear wicked spirits in the dining area?
- I don't think so.
- There's no way for me to know.
It's impossible to hear wicked spirits in the dining area...
- because it's crowded all the time.
- I see.
What did you think of our restaurant today?
- In Yeonhui-dong?
- Yes.
It's the perfect place for people to line up.
- It's perfect.
- So many people will line up.
So we need a fast table turnover.
(A silent pressure directed at the head chef)
There she goes again.
You know what my problem is?
I'm afraid of getting possessed by wicked spirits.
I ordered this to gain less weight,
but I'm eating the whole thing.
I want some fried chicken. We should order it.
It's because you're thinking about having to fry tomorrow.
(Screaming)
(The kitchen talk summons the wicked spirit.)
It's the wicked spirit!
(The wicked spirit has entered.)
My goodness.
Don't even say the word "frying."
I'm sorry, Your Majesty.
Bow down.
(They bow immediately.)
Worship me.
Worship her.
Honesty.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
Bow down.
Get up.
Bow down. Get up.
That's enough.
I want some fried chicken.
(That wasn't the end.)
Goobne Chicken.
"Bake?"
Bake in the oven?
Oven?
(Tteoksagna spirit)
Don't even say the word "oven."
Everyone, bow down.
Get up.
Bow down.
Get up. Bow down.
(Worship me!)
She's possessed by a wicked spirit.
A wicked spirit.
(The wicked spirit is out.)
Isn't it like an episode...
of "Salmokji" where only people...
in the kitchen get possessed?
You can't go to the kitchen...
like in "Train to Busan."
No, you can't.
Or should we just keep it simple...
and make ramyeon for ourselves?
"Ramyeon?"
(Goguryeo Ramyeon spirit)
Goguryeo, Baekje, Silla.
(Goguryeo, Baekje, Silla)
(80km along the sea route southeast of Ulleung Island)
(Exorcism in progress)
(And so...)
What are you going to eat, Yu Jin?
- What are you going to eat?
- Don't eat anything.
I'll drink some water.
A broth?
(Broth spirit)
(A spirit trapped in broth inferno)
Yu Jin, are you going to drink water?
Yu Jin.
(Let's get some sleep for tomorrow's launch event.)
(After a night possessed by wicked spirits)
(Current Time: 12pm)
(The day of the brand launch event arrives.)
(The staff are already busy in broad daylight.)
(A red carpet all the way to the restaurant entrance)
(A photo wall covered with the 2nd branch logo)
(Are they reporters waiting for celebrities?)
(No, they're just the staff taking photos on their phones.)
Here comes Na Yeong Seok.
- Please stand in the center.
- Hello.
Thank you.
(The launch event is ready to go.)
(At Yeonhui-dong)
(The launch party for Space Rice Cake's 2nd branch starts now.)
(Current Time: 1pm)
(A tense atmosphere hangs over the red carpet.)
They're coming.
(The first car is approaching.)
(Who will be the first celebrity to walk the red carpet?)
Here comes Mimi.
(The sous chef makes a chic entrance.)
Hello.
(The press is buzzing with excitement.)
With her potato cream tteoksagna,
she spread the love of rice cakes.
Please look to your right and pose.
(Today, she's here as an idol singer.)
Look to your left.
Could you give us a pose...
to celebrate the launch of the second branch?
Let's go!
(Feeling embarrassed for her)
Why are you so embarrassed?
(It's a misunderstanding.)
(Who could blame him?)
Why are you so embarrassed?
(The low-key event is more violent than expected.)
Thank you.
(The crew is desperately capturing every moment on their phones.)
(The footage is lower quality than the attitude.)
(Working hard)
I couldn't...
let go of the first branch.
So I've been going through a lot emotionally until yesterday.
However, I've been training in the mountains...
and working on myself.
As a martial arts master,
I'm opening 100 franchise branches today!
(The first celebrity enters with a powerful cry for good fortune.)
(A magnificent display of her primary job)
(Let's go, Space Rice Cake!)
She's coming.
(From far away, the second celebrity's ride catches the eye.)
(She arrives radiating serious presence.)
(Unusually upright)
My goodness. Welcome.
(The scooter is parked way too far away.)
(Entering while making eye contact with the viewers)
(Struggling)
(In awe)
Lee Eun Ji is here.
Please come to the photo wall.
(Getting dismantled with the driver's help)
We'll take some photos at the photo wall.
(The hall master, Lee Eun Ji)
Please come to the photo wall.
(A little nod)
(Putting on a hat from those days)
She's being escorted to the entrance.
(Her leopard-print sleeveless top stands out.)
(Entering with an escort like a queen)
I'll take one quick photo with Jude Law.
Please look to your right and pose.
(Double the lethal charm)
(A cozy moment between the artist and the CEO)
Please look to the center.
You may go. Thank you, Jude Law.
Thank you.
Did he come all this way just for this?
Stand in the center.
He really came just for this?
(Trying desperately not to laugh)
He's making a lonely exit.
He's really leaving.
Could you give us a pose to celebrate Space Rice Cake?
Space Rice Cake,
let's go!
Space Rice Cake.
Congratulations on the opening of the second branch.
Until the day we open our 645th branch,
we'll do our best.
Please show our brand lots of love.
Thank you.
It's nonalcoholic.
(It's nonalcoholic champagne.)
(I had a good time.)
- While we were talking, - More people will come.
another chef is making an entrance.
That's great.
(The eco-friendly chef arrives by bicycle.)
My partner, my boss, is coming.
Gosh, here comes Mrs. Ma Bok Rim.
(Too shy to walk the red carpet, she passes by it.)
She can't ride the bicycle.
(There's another parking crisis.)
(Oh, I'm fine.)
She's the head chef of Space Rice Cake.
- That's right.
- Here comes Lee Young Ji.
Our head chef and king.
- It's Lee Young Ji.
- Yes.
Here she comes!
(Please come in.)
She's making her entrance to a huge round of cheers.
- The king is different.
- Let's hear it.
(Immediately putting the spectators in line after getting off)
Louder.
(Cheering)
Okay, please come to the photo wall.
That's not enough. Louder.
(The head chef is enjoying the crowd.)
Please come to the photo wall.
(The character for "patience" to ward off wicked spirits today)
Please stand in the middle.
(She accessorized with a headscarf.)
Chef, you look beautiful.
(A truly professional look)
Please look to the left.
Your glasses look pretty.
(Feeling proud of her)
Your lips are so red...
that they remind me of tteokbokki.
Please look to the middle again.
Give us a pose to celebrate Space Rice Cake.
- Please give us a pose.
- One, two, three.
Let's go.
All right.
- Torong?
- She's miming a kettle.
What's my mindset going into Space Rice Cake?
(Yes!)
Let's go, Young Ji.
- That's great.
- Okay.
They say that it's our Met Gala.
- I see.
- Are we doing it right?
This isn't the look I was expecting.
The person in charge of cuteness is entering.
- Has the genius of service arrived?
- Yes.
Is the youngest of Space Rice Cake here?
Yes, here comes the youngest.
(Finally, the last celebrity arrives.)
All right.
Please make way for her.
My gosh.
(The restaurant part-timer, An Yu Jin)
- Goodness.
- This is it.
This is the Met Gala.
- You look great.
- Is this right?
(The youngest arrives looking like she was at the salon since dawn.)
Hey, is this right?
(Today, she's here as an idol.)
- Oh, my.
- Please come to the photo wall.
Could you give me your hand?
Goodness.
This is it. This is the Met Gala.
Please stand at the center.
- Goodness.
- Please look this way first.
Now it finally looks like the Met Gala.
Look to your left.
(This is IVE's attitude.)
Yes, look to the left first.
(The tall youngest is here.)
- Please look at the center.
- This is really the Met Gala.
- It's truly a photo wall.
- Look to the right.
(We don't want to cover her up, so we'll make the caption smaller.)
Please look at the center again.
- Please give us a pose...
- Her shoulders.
to celebrate Space Rice Cake.
Turn around and look over your shoulder.
- Turn around.
- You have to serve anyway.
(Isn't my position being cute?)
(The winning pose)
Could you say a few words...
to Space Rice Cake's second branch?
- Congratulations...
- Her way of speaking changed.
on the opening of Space Rice Cake's second branch.
(Idol applause)
I hope you make lots of money...
and prosper.
I wish you luck.
- She's talking like...
- Her way of speaking...
- it's someone else's restaurant.
- It's someone else's restaurant.
Her way of speaking changed.
IVE will be cheering you on. Thank you.
She's using her broadcast voice.
(Yu Jin of IVE is cheering for you.)
- All right.
- She's here as an IVE member.
Everyone, please stand in front of the photo wall.
- Hello.
I've heard about you.
These are four influencers who gathered here...
to make this occasion shine.
(I'm especially impressed by your eye makeup.)
I've heard a lot about them.
I see.
This is a very famous brand.
- Excuse me, but...
- Yes?
(Swoosh)
At the center? Yes, you're the king.
- The king.
- We'll stand apart.
- Okay.
Everyone, please look to the left.
To the left.
- I wish you success.
- To the center.
To the center. I wish you luck.
Where's BBC?
Please look at the center again.
Let's do a group pose.
Can you make hearts in pairs?
I'm so honored, Head Chef.
- Thank you so much.
- Me too, Your Highness.
(A pair of idol senior and junior)
(A pair of variety show senior and junior)
We're opening now.
We're going to set off the fireworks.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
To celebrate the opening...
of Space Rice Cake's second branch,
- we'll set off the fireworks.
- No.
One, two, three.
- Congratulations.
(Space Rice Cake)
(Congratulations on the opening of Space Rice Cake's 2nd branch)
(Cheering)
(Kind citizens join in on the celebration.)
(Slightly embarrassed)
- My goodness.
- Louder!
(Gladly)
Thank you, everyone.
Shall we clink glasses?
One, two, three.
- Cheers.
(Cheers)
Since we're officially opening, you may tear off...
- the ribbon and go in.
- All right.
(Climbing the stairs again only one day later)
- The head chef can rip it off.
- She should.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
All right!
(Laughing)
(She's thrilled to rip it off properly this time.)
Don't come.
(How she really feels)
- Goodbye, everyone.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
- It's cool inside.
You startled me.
- What?
- Hello.
- What's going on?
- What?
- Hello.
(Shocked)
What? Am I not welcome here?
(The manager arrives with his piercing flying in the wind.)
- Manager Kwon.
- Why are you here?
Manager Kwon.
- Manager Kwon.
- Hello.
You should've come to South Jeolla Province.
- Thank you so much.
- That was too far.
- I knew this would happen.
- Thank you...
for coming.
- You lost weight.
- Look how he lost weight.
Did business go well?
- It wasn't easy.
- Was everything okay?
- It was no small feat.
- Really?
Anyway...
- Where did you come from?
- From home.
- I mean, did you come from the HQ?
- Yes, from the HQ.
- Where are you from?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm from the HQ.
- I see.
"From home?"
Our business did so well that we moved to Seoul.
We opened our flagship location here.
Shouldn't we have menu items that fit the vibe in Seoul?
Shall we go cook?
- Now?
- Right away?
Get changed into something comfortable.
- Already?
- We thought it was the Met Gala.
You really dressed up for this.
If I had known, I wouldn't have done this.
- No...
- Didn't you see the photo wall?
- We took photos.
- I don't know what you did.
Like the Met Gala, can we get one bathroom selfie before we go?
- Yes, a bathroom selfie.
- Okay.
(Unfortunately, the launch event is over.)
- Please come in.
- Okay.
Oh, my.
- Manager, it's good to see you.
- He's here.
Hello.
- Have you used this before?
- Yes.
(Manager Kwon Sung Jun came to pass on his Seoul recipes.)
- This is for you.
- Is it for me?
- Yes.
- Great, I'm cool-toned.
Everyone, do you know what the concept here is?
- Franchise.
- Handmade burgers.
Exactly. You can tell by looking at that griddle.
- It must be patties.
- It's a burger restaurant.
- Yes.
- Don't you like burgers?
- I like them.
- I really like them.
People mostly know me...
for pasta, risotto, and tiramisu.
- Burgers too?
- Yes.
I'm also confident when it comes to burgers,
so I'll come up with some recipes today.
I will pass them on to you.
(Recipes created exclusively for Space Rice Cake's 2nd branch)
While we do that...
- Can I ask you something?
- What?
- We have to talk about this.
- How many items...
will you remove from the menu?
- I've grown attached to them.
- I see.
- How many will you remove...
- I'm sorry,
but we must approach business with a T mindset.
(An INFP is caught off guard.)
Cut what needs to be cut.
(Today's menu items to learn with a T mindset)
(2 types of burgers, beef and shrimp)
(Mint carrot cake)
(Yuzu radish pickles)
This place has a fast food vibe.
It's like a burger restaurant.
I think pickles would work...
- better than dongchimi.
- They go well together.
(Goheung's yuzu dongchimi...)
(transforms into tangy yuzu radish pickles.)
Sir, should we wash two radishes to start?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I'll get the radish ready.
(After cutting the radish into manageable pieces)
Please watch your fingers,
- Okay.
- or they'll fly off in no time.
(The key is slicing it thinly with a mandoline.)
- Watch your hands.
- Yu Jin, let's keep this setup.
- Let's not change it.
- Yes, use it like this.
Things are so fancy here.
All right.
- Slice the radish into strips.
- Okay.
It's the same process for making any kind of pickle.
You make a pickle brine like this.
Let it cool down. When it reaches around 40°C, add it.
- After cooling it down?
- Yes.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but I already made it.
- That's how you do it.
- You're the best.
Okay, I'll put it in.
(Leave it at room temperature so the flavors can soak in.)
(The first main menu item, rice cake burger)
(Gijeongtteok,)
(basil mayonnaise, arugula,)
(tomato, cheddar cheese,)
(beef patty, basil mayonnaise,)
(and gijeongtteok)
(A beef burger with rice cake buns)
The concept behind this burger is...
a tteokgalbi burger.
- That sounds good.
- That sounds very delicious.
Add 500ml of thick soy sauce.
- Pear juice.
- Yes, add some pear juice.
Since we have to wait for it to cook...
(Cook it down until it's reduced by half)
- Shall we make basil pesto?
- Yes.
(Meanwhile, they make basil pesto.)
- I'm good at making basil pesto.
- I know.
- Olive oil, basil...
- Oh, come on.
I know it all. Parmelino pporejilo...
- What?
- and pporeuppangtto cheese.
What did you say?
Do I make the basil pesto that I used for basil tteokbokki?
That's correct.
- Okay.
- Let's make a smoothie.
- Smoothie. Start.
- Start. Okay.
(Making basil pesto)
My Goheung.
(Grind the mentality... I mean, grind the basil well.)
How am I as the human blender?
- It's great.
- It's very good.
(Tasting the basil mayonnaise)
- It tastes amazing.
- It's delicious.
Young Ji, it tastes so good.
- Goodness.
- It's insanely good.
- Mimi, prepare the rice cakes.
- Okay.
(They plan to make buns with gijeongtteok instead of bread.)
This must be the signature item.
- Cut them all out with the mold.
- Okay.
(Using a round mold to cut out the gijeongtteok)
Gosh, they look so nice and round.
(Round rice cake buns are ready.)
- Next up is...
- It's the patty.
Patty.
- Do I pour all the meat?
- Yes, please.
(Add the ground chuck eye roll first.)
Add 105g of beef tallow.
What's beef tallow?
It's this. It's beef fat.
We don't know the technical terms.
"Beef tallow" isn't a technical term.
- Beef fat.
- It just means beef fat.
- Isn't the word still technical?
- Of course.
I guess so.
When making a patty, you usually mix in some fat.
- We'll add tteokgalbi seasoning.
- Okay.
Add 14 spoonfuls of breadcrumbs.
- Mimi, keep mixing them.
- Okay.
(Mix them thoroughly.)
Here's what you do.
(It's time to knead the patty.)
Bring it together into a ball first.
(Smacking)
- Okay.
- Think about someone...
- who gets on your nerves.
- Okay.
- Lee Young Ji!
- Goodness.
You got it, right?
Chef, is this...
- Yes.
- how you do it?
- Neapolitan.
- Goodness.
- "Neapolitan?"
- What's wrong with that?
It's a little small.
- It's only 140g.
- At the end.
Gosh, they're really fat.
(Plump beef patties are ready.)
- The patties are ready.
- We can move on.
- What's next?
- Everything is set up here.
All the burger ingredients are here.
(Buttering the griddle)
- Cook the bottoms first.
- Two at a time?
(Rice cake buns hit the griddle first.)
- It sounds like rain.
- My gosh.
It sounds like making jeon.
It'd be nice to cook jeon on the griddle.
- That sounds delicious.
- Deejaying.
Okay, that looks good.
(Grill the gijeongtteok to Welsh Corgi-like golden brown)
- Okay.
- Stay calm.
(Nice and golden)
Let's cook the patties.
All right. Just flip them.
Head chef, let's go.
Nice, head chef.
(The cheering squad)
That's useful advice.
- Treat it like a baby.
- Do it well.
- That's very good.
- Treat it like a baby.
- Nice.
- Okay.
- I'll press it down lightly.
Here's how you do it. Support it underneath...
and press in a cross shape.
(Pressing in a cross pattern to cook it all the way through)
- It's an advanced technique.
- It looks like a commercial.
Girls, this is an advanced technique.
Put on a slice of cheese.
(One yellow blanket of cheese)
Cheese has to be melted. Pour some water and cover it.
- My gosh.
- That's amazing.
Then it melts right away.
- That's great. It's very sexy.
- Right?
Split the gijeongtteok in half.
(Split the gijeongtteok in half.)
Basil mayonnaise.
Patty.
- Put on a slice of tomato.
- Tomato.
- Arugula.
And...
- Basil mayonnaise.
- Now it's done.
- It's done.
- Okay.
(The beef burger set with potato puffs is complete.)
- It looks so beautiful.
- It really does.
It's pretty.
I'm bad at decorating it.
- You're doing well.
Dirty pantries are popular...
- these days.
- "Dirty pantries?"
(Actually, dirty plating is what's trendy.)
- Delicious.
- It's done.
It looks perfect.
- That's it.
- Great.
I love it so much.
(It's time to taste it.)
(The head chef takes a bite first.)
(Exclaiming)
- Gosh, it's so good.
- Really?
- Chef, it's really good.
- What is this?
The rice cake buns don't taste out of place at all.
- Right?
- This is quite good.
The basil mayonnaise is the secret weapon.
It's insanely good.
(Very excited)
- It's really good.
- Let's get rid of the tteokbokki.
- Right?
- Get rid of it.
- I forgot all about...
- my pollack roe and clam pasta.
- Forget it.
We don't need it anymore.
Just like love is forgotten through love,
- I got a new boyfriend.
- food is...
- Food is forgotten through food.
- We got a new boyfriend.
(The second main menu item, shrimp burger)
(A plump shrimp patty with punchy wasabi mayo sauce)
There's a separate sauce for shrimp burgers.
- Wasabi.
- That looks delicious.
- Wasabi mayonnaise.
- It looks good.
- And we'll add this to it.
- What is it? A log?
- It's not a log.
- Coconut?
- Yam?
- It's called horseradish.
- I love horseradish so much.
- It's delicious.
Think of it as Western-style wasabi.
Like white radish?
I love mayonnaise. I want to put it in my mouth.
The sauce is the key.
- I thought it would be.
- It has to turn out well.
The sauce is the key.
(Mix the sauce well.)
We'll grind half of the shrimp.
- The other half...
- Add as is?
- will be finely chopped.
- Okay.
- Why? For the texture.
- For the texture.
(Half is roughly chopped with two knives.)
- That's very good.
- It's like a performance.
(The other half is finely processed.)
- Mimi, watch it carefully.
- Okay.
(Add peeled shrimp, cornstarch, olive oil, and chopped parsley.)
It looks so good.
(Once the mixture is ready, shape it into patties.)
We shape it by hand.
- Exactly. Keep it even and pat.
- Pat.
- It turns round when you fry it.
- Okay.
We need to pack it together...
- and make it wide.
- Wide?
- Wider than rice cakes.
- About this big.
- Okay.
- Isn't it too thin?
- No, that's okay.
- It's okay.
- Flour, eggs, breadcrumbs.
- In that order.
Don't forget the sides.
Put it in carefully like this.
It's good to shake off...
- the breadcrumbs.
- Shake them off before putting in.
Like that...
For how long?
- Fry it for five minutes.
- Five minutes?
(Deep-fry the shrimp patties at 170°C for 5 to 6 minutes)
- They're ready.
- They will be so good.
(Once the shrimp patties are fried to golden brown)
If you put in too much, it could be too potent.
You can apply it on both sides.
It was a little sharp.
Since it's wasabi, control the amount.
The shrimp patties will be amazing.
- Like this.
- I love it with romaine lettuce.
- Patty, onions.
- Right here.
(Red onions)
(It looks a little strange now.)
It looks so good.
(We plan to make it like this.)
(Plump)
Try to eat mostly the patty.
(It's time to taste it.)
It's hard to cut the rice cake.
Done.
Now.
- This...
- The shrimp flavor...
- tastes great.
- It has strong shrimp flavor.
It's so good.
It's good.
(Mimi, who worked hard mincing shrimp, is satisfied too.)
- Nice.
- It's so delicious.
(Shrimp burger is a success too!)
Kwon Sung Jun.
(Dessert: Mint carrot cake)
(Pot-shaped carrot rice cake)
- Today's highlight.
Carrot cake.
I've been waiting for this.
The base is mint cream.
Some people don't like mint. Will it be okay?
- Carrot...
- Exactly. Mint is...
- I'm a bit worried.
- Not everyone likes carrots too.
- But why mint...
- I like it.
- Do you?
- Me too.
- Then we'll go with it.
- I don't like it.
- Convince me.
- Okay.
I'll convince you.
(He starts convincing her!)
- One of you...
- Yes, chef.
- Do I mince it?
- Mince the remaining gijeongtteok.
- Yes, chef.
- We're aiming for zero waste.
We can't have food waste.
- What we used to cut just now...
- That's right.
- You're going to use it.
- The remaining pieces.
I'll mince it.
- Yes, chef. What should I do?
- Then, Yu Jin.
- Yes, chef.
- You'll work on the mint cream.
I'll add a ton of mascarpone cheese.
(Mascarpone cheese)
- I'll add 100g of whipped cream.
- Okay.
(Whipped cream)
- Look at the color.
- Good.
Chef, it has a scary color.
- That's how mint syrup looks.
- The color...
It's my first time seeing mint syrup.
The color is like poison.
This is how the color looks.
It's so scary.
(Add the ingredients and mix them using a whisk.)
The color... It's scary.
(Thick mint cream is ready.)
- Next is carrot rice cake.
- Okay.
Add one cup of carrot juice.
Carrot juice.
Carrots, which Torong likes.
- Carrot juice, which Torong likes.
- Bunny
- Torong is a rabbit.
- Carrot
I know that. Knead it strongly.
(Knead the dough strongly with her hands!)
Nice.
Like a king's artist,
make the shape.
- And...
- Yu Jin is good.
- You're good, Yu Jin.
- This is fun.
Yu Jin is good with her hands.
You're right.
That's Jeju Island carrot.
Nice carrot.
- Let's deep-fry it.
- You're deep-frying it?
- At 180°C.
- They look cute floating up.
- Really? Are they cute?
They suddenly pop up...
- like this.
- That's so cute. They puffed up.
(Well-fried carrots)
The carrots look nice.
They really look like carrots.
(Make stems using rosemary.)
It looks like a real carrot.
- Here comes the plating.
- Plating.
- Yuzu marmalade.
- You use yuzu marmalade too?
Remember the leftover gijeongtteok?
Yes. Next, mint cream.
Use a lot.
(A lot of mint cream on top of it)
- Sponge cake.
Cocoa crumble.
And the cherry on top.
- Carrot.
- The cherry on top.
It really looks like a pot.
(Carrot rice cake)
- One more.
(Place a shovel spoon on it.)
- Good.
- Nice.
Neapolitan Matpia.
Kwon Sung Jun.
Let's taste it, shall we?
- Yes.
- I'm scared.
(Starting with Eun Ji, who loves mint)
Try the carrot too.
I like it.
Because I like carrots and mint.
- Try it.
- The cream is good.
(Carrot rice cake made of sticky rice)
- It's like a sticky rice donut.
- Yes.
(It's chewy like a sticky rice donut!)
Doesn't it taste like sticky rice donut?
(The mint hater tries it.)
- I don't know about that.
- I think so.
(Satisfied)
It's nice.
The mint isn't that strong, so it's fine.
- The mint isn't strong.
- Some of them hit you strongly.
- Have we learned everything?
- It's good.
That's the end of the recipes.
- All we need is practice.
- Practice is the only way to go.
(The long recipe-learning is over!)
We're going to accept reservations...
- Yes.
- using this app.
It'll be nice to write an introduction of the restaurant...
and the menu items you just made.
It sounds fun.
It has pictures.
(For the 2nd branch, they'll adopt a reservation system.)
(On the reservation app, they'll write...)
(the description of the restaurant, the menu, and the price.)
(They'll accept customers online.)
"Restaurant name, Space Rice Cake second branch."
- Okay.
- A one-sentence description.
- We need to introduce our shop.
How should we introduce it?
"Please don't come, if possible."
Hold on, head chef.
Do as you like, head chef.
Chef.
"Please don't come, if possible."
"It's hard to do business."
This makes you want to go even more in a way.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- It triggers your rebellious side.
- That's right.
It makes them want to go.
"There are too many reservations."
(It actually is a high-level noise marketing.)
(Next, the restaurant description)
Introduce our restaurant.
(She types without stopping again.)
Hold on.
She wrote, "The restaurant is full of burnouts."
(Revealing their mental states to the whole world)
"The restaurant is full of burnouts."
"You may be possessed by evil spirits,"
"so make sure to sprinkle salt before coming in."
"However, when you visit,"
"we'll do our best to provide good service."
(Regardless of the burnout, they guarantee good service and taste.)
Let's write humility and so on at the end.
- "Honesty, humility, ahk."
- Done.
- It's nice.
It's done.
(The description of Space Rice Cake 2nd branch is complete.)
- Next, menu.
- Opening hours.
- "Add menu."
- "Category, main."
- "Main."
Beef burger and shrimp burger that we learned today.
We'll serve them.
There's something I want to add to all the burgers.
- Let's hear it out.
- Fatty shrimp burger,
fatty beef burger.
- I want to add it.
- "Fatty."
Head chef, but for our dishes,
- we must add "rice cake."
- Yes.
Fatty rice cake...
Fat rice. Rice fatty cake...
Fat rice, rice fat,
rice fatty rice.
Fatty rice fatty cake.
- Then...
- Rice fatty rice cake.
Fatty rice cake doesn't sound all that cute.
Much rice cake burger or too much rice cake in a burger.
Too much rice cake in a burger?
- That's good.
- I like that.
- That's nice.
- Too much rice cake in a burger?
Much rice cake burger. Rice cake burger burger.
Too much rice cake in a burger.
It sticks when you add "too much."
Too much rice cake in a burger
The patty slid in
(Adding rhythm to the menu)
(Everything she sings becomes a bop.)
- Let's do it.
- Hold on. What is it?
Too much rice cake in a burger
The patty slid in
(Choreography has been added.)
It has choreography too. Like Brown Eyed Girls...
Too much rice cake in a burger
The patty slid in
That's right.
You're good.
There's this too.
Too much rice cake in a burger
Plump shrimp pop
(Deeply moved)
(The lyrics-writing factory never rests.)
Plump shrimp pop
- Tell me the lyrics again.
- On a happy day...
"Too much rice cake in a burger."
"Beef inside the rice cake."
- "Beef inside the rice cake."
- Isn't it "slid in?"
Beef slid inside the rice cake
It's been rearranged a bit.
("Too Much Rice Cake in a Burger" remix version)
Too much rice cake in a burger
- Beef...
- Beef slid in
- That's it.
- "Beef..."
- What about shrimp?
- Shrimp...
- Plump shrimp.
- Hold on.
It's too much for me.
- Too much for Eun Ji - Too much for Eun Ji
Her mannerism pops
Plump shrimp pop
- "Pop."
"With tater tots and a soft drink."
(Main menu registered)
- Done.
- Let's go.
- It looks good.
I'd like to decide on one thing first.
How much was original tteokbokki small?
- Nine dollars.
- That price is impossible...
in Yeonhui-dong.
(Agreed)
Let's add another 0, so it's 90 dollars.
(Exponential price increase)
We reflected Goheung's price level,
based on the shops around.
- There's the rent to consider.
- This two-storey building,
which we didn't even want.
- We have two floors now.
- We didn't want it.
- I'm stumped.
- Then...
why don't we serve bigger rice cakes?
Increase both the portion and the price.
And the quality too.
Three each.
(They'll increase the portion to match the price.)
Yes, and now, we need to decide the name.
I suggest changing original tteokbokki...
to Lee Young Ji tteokbokki.
We must do it!
- I think we can do it.
- Finally.
- Finally, you're putting your name.
- Let's do it.
Yeonhui-dong... We've made it.
How will you explain this rice cake?
It's Lee Young Ji...
original tteokbokki!
(Satisfied)
This is Lee Young Ji original tteokbokki.
She's pushing herself today.
She's using every bit of her soul.
The last of her strengths.
- My trapezius muscle is pulling.
- Exactly.
Okay. Nice.
Let's go.
- Will you be okay?
- Pollack roe and clam pasta.
Let's go with tteoksagna.
- We have an oven, so it's fine.
- Tteoksagna.
- Potato cream tteoksagna.
Please explain it in detail.
- Tell us.
- Write it in the way you speak.
Write whatever comes...
to your mind.
Tell me right now.
Potato cream sticky rice cake...
- That...
Sprinkle cheese,
put it in the oven,
it's hot, you can't burn yourself,
anyway, if it comes out delicious, it's done.
(Potato cream sticky rice cake... Sprinkle cheese, it's hot...)
(Reflecting her pronunciation 100 percent)
(It's clearly Mimi's menu.)
(Grade 1 in Mimi Language)
She wrote exactly how Mi Hyun spoke.
(Potato cream tteoksagna, potato cream sticky rice cake...)
(Goheung dish again)
What do you think about carrot cake? Team Dessert.
"Do you like me? Of carrot cake." How is it?
(Do you like me? Of carrot!)
(Do you love me? Of carrot!)
(I love you, you love me)
(Carrot!)
- It's so cute. Can you continue?
- Continue singing.
- I'll sing.
- Can you do that?
I have an opinion.
How does "do you like mint" sound?
"Do you like mint? Of carrot."
(Do you like mint? Of carrot!)
- That's good.
- You need "mint" in the name...
- so they won't get taken aback.
- I agree.
And since people either like or hate mint,
this is cute.
- Do you like mint? Of carrot cake.
- I love it.
- Do you like mint?
- It needs to be under dessert.
Do you like mint? Of carrot! Cake.
Make it sound like Torong.
- Torong.
- "I eat this every day."
- Done.
- New.
- New dessert.
- Let's go.
Okay.
Let me know if you want to edit any information from here.
- No.
- I wrote whatever I wanted.
Add menu... Hold on.
I want to add one.
What are you going to do?
I'm worried.
(They've finished writing all the menu items to sell.)
(The menu makes them laugh.)
- "Lee Eun Ji's performance?"
- Wait.
- What kind of menu is that?
- It'll become...
an entertainment establishment.
We'll become an entertainment establishment.
She's writing "Mamma Mia!," "Moulin Rouge!," and "Kinky Boots."
We can't do that.
"When she's having a mannerism,"
"please refrain from ordering."
- "She is our precious employee."
- "Employee."
- "Performer."
The price.
Just a pinch of cuteness.
Done.
(Lee Eun Ji's performance, various musical numbers available,)
(order closed when she's having a mannerism issue)
(All menu items have been registered.)
Today's staff meal was going to be burgers.
- It so happened.
- But...
you learned how to cook burgers.
- Yes.
- So we'll order half...
from another store,
and you'll cook the remaining half...
so they can pick and choose.
Today's staff meal was going to be burgers.
- It so happened.
- But...
you learned how to cook burgers.
- Yes.
- So we'll order half...
from another store,
and you'll cook the remaining half...
so they can pick and choose.
(It's a burger showdown.)
(15 sets of burgers)
(10 sets of desserts)
(They must finish them in 60 minutes.)
(Intense evaluations will be taking place.)
- I'm scared.
- You're even doing...
- mock reviews?
- Yes.
What if they upload strange reviews?
Instead, we'll do this for you.
Consider it a practice...
and ordering a staff meal.
We'll pay half the price...
- of what you make.
- Okay.
- Half the price.
- I'm nervous.
- It's 7:40pm now.
You'll start cooking after five minutes.
- Beef...
- Fifteen.
- Okay, 15.
- How about 8?
- And ten desserts.
- Okay.
Ten carrot cakes.
(They must finish by 8:45pm.)
(Running)
What is it again? Eight beef and eight shrimp?
Eight beef, seven shrimp.
- Hello.
- Wash your hands.
- The bump is dangerous.
- Be careful.
- I almost tripped.
- What should we do first?
I'll chop the vegetables.
The cutting board...
(Where's the cutting board?)
Where's the cutting board?
Where's the knife?
Memorizing this...
What are you looking for?
- The bread cutter.
- It's over there.
We just need to make ten?
Is this chuck eye roll?
(They did learn something,)
(but their memories have evaporated.)
(They can't remember anything.)
Mint cream...
(She follows her teacher's teachings.)
Nice.
This is...
The cameramen filming this will be eating, so the process...
- Don't worry.
- Hygiene!
Don't worry.
Hygiene!
(They engraved "hygiene" in their hearts.)
Director, hygiene.
(The director is surprised.)
Hygiene.
(Starts to appeal to the soon-to-be customer.)
So cute.
Director, hygiene.
(Creepy)
(Even as she unwraps the cheese)
So hygienic.
(Even as she minces shrimp)
It takes about eight minutes.
It's hygienic, isn't it?
Hygiene.
(Chopping)
You sound like a master chef.
Exactly.
Director, I put my love in it.
Hygiene.
It has our love in it.
(Promotion over)
You have 20 minutes left.
That's impossible.
(But the rice cake buns look...)
(She's become silent.)
Some of them are cooked well.
What a pity.
These two are fine.
(Looking away)
(She'll use the ones that look fine.)
Yu Jin, should I make ten carrots first?
- Gijeongtteok...
- Yes, Eun Ji.
- Make carrot rice cakes first.
- Carrot rice cakes.
(What Rabbit Eun Ji needs to do)
(Making 10 carrot rice cakes)
(Deep-frying 10 carrot rice cakes)
Cutting the bun makes me nervous.
You can do it.
It's hot.
(Actually, this rice cake bun...)
(was cooked on the hot griddle.)
(Freshly delivered from a 170°C griddle)
(Groaning)
(Grunting)
- It's hot, right?
- Young Ji.
Cut off the ugly part.
Where? It's hot.
(You may not have asked, Young Ji, but my hands are fine.)
Buns are ready.
(Rice cake buns are set.)
Five minutes.
- Okay.
- My gosh.
Beef burgers are ready.
Hash browns are cooking nicely.
- Hash browns?
- Not hash browns.
- You surprised me.
I'm sorry.
I better not say anything.
(Space Rice Cake)
(Meanwhile, the dessert enemy has arrived at the doorstep.)
(The burger enemy joins.)
(The staff who received the burgers walks in quickly.)
The food has been delivered.
We can do it.
You think we can't?
- You think we can't?
- Mi Hyun, what are you doing now?
We'll improvise it somehow,
and if we ruin it, we'll just practice again.
Yes. This...
Just because I lose to another restaurant today...
- doesn't mean my life is ruined.
- Of course.
(Her pronunciation has suddenly improved.)
- One minute left.
- What?
- One minute left?
- Yes.
(Meanwhile, the enemy is approaching.)
(A fearsome entry of burgers)
(The enemy takes the high ground first.)
Oh, my gosh.
(On the other hand, they have nothing ready.)
(Current time: 8:45pm)
(Time's up.)
(And...)
(The dinner announcement has been sent.)
(There are burgers on the 2nd floor! Enjoy your meal.)
(The tasting panelists enter one after another in hunger.)
(To the place where there's too much rice cake in burgers)
(They approach closer.)
Let's serve a few of them together.
- We're doing well.
I'll just serve one.
- There's only one option.
- Exactly.
This is all?
It's not here.
(Rice cake burger isn't here.)
I guess I'll take this.
(The customers they missed in the beginning...)
- What's that?
- Shrimp burger.
(are quite many.)
- The last one.
- You're five minutes behind.
- What should we do?
- We can do it.
- We need to get going.
Send the carrot rice cakes up first.
Can I physically block them from taking the other burgers?
- I think that's a good idea.
- Yu Jin, take carrot rice cakes.
Yu Jin, what do we do?
Shall we serve the ones that are done first?
Send the complete ones up first.
The meal time has started,
so they'll be going up one by one.
Guys, what do we do?
Yu Jin, go up with the complete ones.
- Do I really go up?
- Yes, go up first.
We need to serve something.
They're going up.
What should we do?
Yu Jin, what should we do?
- Here.
- The stairs are hard to climb,
so we need to bring a few more when we go up.
- What do we do, Yu Jin?
- Just three more.
- This is insane.
- You're doing great.
- You're doing well.
- What do we do?
- I'll just put one.
(Rushing)
(She moves quickly like a rabbit.)
Where should I set this?
Where should I set this? What's this?
Yu Jin, where do I set this?
(Yu Jin is on the 1st floor.)
You should eat tasty food.
A burger made of rice cake.
(She manages to serve it somehow.)
Yu Jin... Hello.
Hello. Please hold on.
Our food is on the way too.
Ours is coming.
Hello.
Delicious burgers have arrived.
Excuse me.
It's really delicious. It's cute, right?
Enjoy.
(Running)
Now that I'm in a hurry, I can just run up the stairs.
Exactly. Remember what I said?
I just end up doing it.
(1 rice cake burger)
(2 rice cake burgers)
(Although they're late,)
(Space Rice Cake's burgers are catching up.)
You've exceeded ten minutes.
Shall we go up one more time?
- Please go one more time.
- One more time.
(She hurriedly goes to deliver.)
Gosh, you should try this.
(But...)
- I want to try the shrimp burger.
- Me too.
(Shrimp burgers are still nowhere to be seen.)
This is cardio.
(Shrimp burgers are coming.)
- Shrimp burgers.
- They're warm.
If you wait a little longer, you can get warm shrimp burgers.
If you want shrimp burgers, please wait for a bit.
Shrimp burgers on the way.
You want more shrimp burgers?
Director.
Your shrimp burger.
(She's practically a shrimp burger ambassador.)
Who wants shrimp burgers?
(Thanks to the ambassador, shrimp burgers are popular.)
Most of the staff have gone up.
Only the cameramen here are left.
- Our team.
- Please go.
Uno, Dos, Cuatro...
Please make a good choice.
We worked hard!
(Meanwhile, Cameraman Cuatro faces the burger he always shot.)
You want a shrimp burger, don't you?
Freshly made shrimp burger. Enjoy!
(Delivery complete)
(Delayed by 13 minutes)
I feel like I'm losing weight.
- I don't know. I think...
- Now, you...
can take a break and wait for the reviews.
- Okay.
He brought it here.
You're going to eat it in front of us?
They can make their reviews like that.
Don't spill it.
Are you done?
- The bread and...
- Are you done?
- Do you want more?
- No thanks.
- Do you need a refill?
- I'm fine.
- You're fine?
- I had enough.
- Tell me if you need more.
- You don't give refills.
I have more hash browns here.
We're slow, but the food tastes good.
They're writing negative comments.
- Their reviews...
- Are you writing negative comments?
They are writing their reviews. They're criticizing us.
- Where are they?
- Right in front of us.
(Monitoring the cameramen)
They're done eating.
(Just then)
(Do desserts not come with spoons?)
(I also don't have a spoon.)
(Neither do I! How are we supposed to eat this?)
(They made a critical mistake.)
The shrimp burgers...
Did you not serve the carrot dessert with spoons?
(The panelists would be eating like cranes now.)
- This is beef, right?
- Yes.
The shovels are here. We forgot these.
- We were in a rush.
- That's right.
(Feeling bad)
I'm sorry!
(The evaluation begins.)
- I'm so nervous.
- Goodness.
Will we hear them here?
(Wobbling)
Goodness. You must be so anxious.
Should we go back a step?
How anxious is he that he's shaking so much?
(Putting on a brave face out of anxiety)
Despite the friendship we've built...
First, the reason they chose burgers from outside.
This is a shared opinion.
Because ours comes out late.
They chose to get burgers from outside...
because ours comes out late.
We can't do anything about that because we learned it just today.
No restaurant learns a menu in one day...
- That's right.
- and starts prepping right away.
Right. This is an opinion by one of the producers.
"I wanted a rice cake burger, but it took so long to come out."
This is from the fixed-camera team.
"I couldn't eat it..."
- "because it came out so late."
- The fixed-camera team.
You couldn't eat because you were filming it,
not because it came out late.
Those were the comments.
What about the comments on the taste?
The comments on the taste.
This is from a writer.
Beef burger, four stars.
- Four.
- Four?
"The beef patty was twice as big as the ones outside."
"It'd be a waste not to eat it. It still tastes good when cold"
(The first positive comment)
The beef burger really got cold.
Still, they gave us a good evaluation. Thank you.
This is also from a writer.
Beef burger, five stars.
The chewy rice cake made it more fun to eat than a burger with bread.
- It has an interesting texture.
- Right. It has a fun texture.
Those were the good comments.
- Is that all?
- Now come...
- the so-so comments.
- The so-so ones.
It's from the camera team.
"It tasted great considering how it was made."
(Cameraman in charge of Young Ji)
"The shrimp patty also tasted good."
"Even though I usually like wasabi, it was still too sharp."
"It would have been nice if the fries were crispier."
He saw the process of making the rice cakes from the very front.
He would have had so many doubts when we were making it.
- But it tasted good, right?
- What a relief.
- Tasty, right? Weren't you shocked?
- It's such a relief.
This is also...
- an ambiguous review.
- Ambiguous.
There are four stars, though. It's from the camera team.
I chose it because I was curious...
after seeing the process from the very front.
(Cameraman in charge of Mimi)
"I was satisfied..."
"with the crispiness of the shrimp patty."
"It tasted good because it had a lot of shrimp."
(Cameraman in charge of Mimi)
"I was disappointed because the rice cake bun fell apart,"
- "which made it difficult to eat."
- Oh, no.
- I'm sorry. We'll try to fix that.
- At the end...
- That's what it says.
We rushed at the end.
From the fixed-camera team,
this person chose the beef burger.
"I wonder if the person who made it chopped onions before."
"I smell onions even though there are no onions."
My goodness.
- How did that person know that?
- That's the worst.
- Did you do it right after that?
- This is a bit sad.
- Right.
- Goodness.
- We have to think about that.
- I should use this.
Those were the overall comments on the burgers.
(Evaluations on the rice cake burgers: Better than expected...)
(considering how it was made, but often with a strong onion smell)
- Moving on to the carrot cake.
- Carrot cake.
- We forgot to serve...
the shovels with the carrot cakes.
Forgetting to serve the shovels... Isn't that like picking a fight?
- Help yourselves.
These are the comments.
"What I liked was the refreshing and tasty mint cream."
"But I almost ate with my hands..."
"because it wasn't served with a shovel spoon."
"It also had a strong chocolate flavor..."
"because there wasn't enough gijeongtteok and castella."
- I'm sorry.
- That's right. We did that.
Also...
This is from the fixed-camera team.
"I didn't take the carrot cake because I don't like mint."
(A review expressing a dislike)
- Do you like mint?
- Some people don't like it.
But it could taste good once you try it.
- I should say that tomorrow.
- That's right.
A writer gave three stars and commented...
It must be a negative one.
"It was filled lower than the cup,"
"so I wondered if they had gone light with the ingredients,"
"but everything balanced out well when eaten together."
That's a relief. It tasted good.
- Right.
- It tasted good.
And this...
could be a harsh one.
Yu Jin!
- The person gave four stars.
- Four stars isn't bad.
"It's a unique taste I haven't tried before."
"The mint flavor wasn't that strong."
"But I would wonder whether I should eat it..."
"considering it costs eight dollars."
Right. We made a mistake on the portion size.
Also, "I picked up a fork from the hallway..."
"because there was no spoon."
(Spoon again)
It wasn't just one spoon missing?
- All of them.
- They all had no spoon.
That makes it fair.
I should have noticed the spoon.
- We were rushing.
- You were helping us out.
We should have focused on the dessert.
They had no spoon...
- That's...
- We did this and that.
- That's right.
- I suddenly assembled things...
- Right.
- and sliced buns.
That's right. That won't happen tomorrow.
- How many things did I do?
- Tomorrow.
- That won't happen tomorrow.
- Okay.
So for the carrot cake,
you could increase the portion size.
- Just increase the portion size.
- Yes.
And balance the proportions better.
Also, don't forget the shovel spoons.
Don't forget the shovel spoons.
We just learned this for the first time, you know.
- Seriously...
- Well done.
We did really well.
- That's what I think.
- You really did well.
- Honesty, humility, ahk.
(Coming up next, Seoul)
(The D-Day for their first business in Seoul!)
(Don't lose your smiles. Keep smiling.)
(Let's have a happy time.)
(We have an order!)
- Okay! We have an order.
- Right.
(Time to get to work)
(They thought everything would run smoothly.)
(Challenge 1: An unfamiliar POS system)
(Challenge 2: A new workflow)
(Climbing the stairs over and over again)
(Number 5 is done.)
(Her soul left her body.)
(Mannerism overload)
(Challenge 3: A messed-up order)
(Potato cream tteoksagna coming up!)
(We already made potato cream tteoksagna.)
(Space Rice Cake is falling apart.)
(After a hectic lunch rush)
(No one came alone because it's dinner time.)
(There are groups of 4 people.)
(What am I going to do with my life?)
(So someone's here to help.)
(I've come to place an order.)
Goodness!
What brings you here?
(Who is the part-time worker...)
(who came to Space Rice Cake in crisis?)
(Space Rice Cake)